好，你完成了！
All right.
You're done.
来看看我的实现
Let's look at my solution.
首先，我希望你用了笔记中的projection
First, I hope you grabbed
the projection from the notes.
因为我们要填充一个ListView，我们需要一个WeatherEntry ID
Since we're populating a list view,
we need a weather entry ID, but
但是因为我们有一个表连接
since we have a join,
we have to specify this ID precisely
所以我们需要用表名+点+列名来指定我们需要的那个表的ID
with a table name followed by the dot
followed by the column name syntax.
我们不需要使用所有的这些列
We're not using all of these columns.
但是，定义这些常数会让代码可读性更强
But, having these constant defined
will help us keep the code
使我们之后的修改代码更容易
compatible with the updates we
are doing in the next lessons.
这些序号是和projection绑定的
Of course, these indices
are tied to our projection.
如果FORECAST_COLUMNS改变了，也需要修改这些常数
If the forecast columns changes,
we have to modify these accordingly.
在onCreateLoader()中，我们将FORECAST_COLUMNS
In onCreateLoader we then pass
FORECAST_COLUMNS as the projection
作为projection传入CursorLoader的构造器
into our CursorLoader constructor.
最后，我们来修改下在Forecast Adapter中的
Finally, we can fix
a convertCursorRowToUSFormat within our
convertCursorRowToUSFormat()，看看使用这些常数的优点
forecast adapter to take advantage
of these declared indices.
就是这样，我们完成了！
And that's it, we're done.
运行下
Lets run it.
这和我们上次运行时的样子差不多
And it looks exactly like
the last time we run it.
只有这一节是这样
[LAUGH] Is pretty typical for
this section.
不过好消息是没什么Bug
But the good news is that
it's still working correctly.
并且更效率了点
And, it's a little more efficient.
在Lesson5中构建更精细的UI时
We're going to take more
advantage of this in lesson five
我们能体会到它的更多的优点
as we make more sophisticated
user interfaces.